Sorry to keep you waiting, it's about to start.
With Mizuho Ono of Tsubaki Factory,
Beyonce Amenomori I am Minami Okamura from Kawakami.
These two will be presenting this time, so please bear with me until the end.
This distribution date, September 27th, is the day of Tsubaki Factory's new single
Tsubaki Factory's new single "Yuuki! Tsumai Life! If you're just delusional, you can be free! The leader, Riko Yamagishi's last single.
This is the last single of the leader, Riko Yamagishi,
I hope many people will pick it up. I hope many of you will pick it up.
Beyonce and I performed at our first overseas event.
At the time of this recording, we haven't finished the event yet, but by the time you are watching it, we hope that it will have been successfully completed.
I hope you all had a great time at the concert, and I hope you enjoyed the show.
I will be performing a spin show filled with the history of Hello Project's 25th anniversary,
I hope to be able to make the Thai audience excited and excited on the stage.
Well, Tourki Factory is also scheduled to perform in Hong Kong on October 14 and in Taiwan on October 15.
This will be our first overseas performance as well as our first solo performance.
It will also be my first time in Hong Kong and Taiwan, so I'm looking forward to eating the local food there.
Tsubaki Factory will start Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2023 Autumn Shintani Yoga on October 7.
The final concert of the tour will be held at Nippon Budokan on November 6, and it will be the first time in a year and a half for Tsubaki Factory to perform at the Budokan.
It will be the first time for Tsubaki Factory to perform at the Budokan in a year and a half, and it will be the first time for us to perform at a standing Budokan, so we are really looking forward to it, and we will do our best for each and every performance.
And we, the Beyons, are going to play the lead role in the stage play, "Biospy, the Missing Attache Case".
The story is set in Japan, a futuristic city facing east and west from the center of Tokyo, where Beyonce is a spy and how she will complete her mission to deliver an attaché case by 7 pm tonight,
It's going to be a thrilling story. Please look forward to it!
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look. Please watch! Fade up like a good thing!
Let his words roll off your tongue
Tell me what's wrong with him.
I don't want to know!
Ah Ah Ah Ah
In front of everyone, I want to draw a blank
I want to fall in love with a lie
My ideals always seem to hurt
Everyday, Everynight, Elligan-esque
Everyday, everynight, like erigan
Romance.
What's wrong with that?
You're free to fantasize about anything
Older than you and younger than you
If it's just a fantasy, it's free
A girl is Ehime
Sleepless Maiden
You to be a
Don't be reborn
Don't dream
Save her
Hold me close, for real, somebody
I know you're lonely and you're crying
But the times are wise.
I don't need to be strong
Gimme more
The bright light...
Does it hurt anymore?
Move me more
Ola, ola, ola, ola, ola, ola, ola, ola
Blow me away beyond my desires
Cinderella without a jump
I'm more the same than bitter
Ah, they've been eating each other
I want to be loved, even if I'm weak, even if I'm stupid
I'm weak, I'm stupid, I want to be loved
But, but, but... I can do it.
If it's just a fantasy, then I'm free
I'll move on to the middle of the road Love Love Love
If only in my delusion, I'm free
I'm strong and I'm a big lump
I'm delusional, I'm moving
If it breaks, you're overreacting Love Love Love
Desire timid and unstable
If it's only a fantasy, then I'm free and I'm on my way Love Love Love, strong, big ball, move me more
Oresama, ore-sama, la-la-la-la-la
Loop ball, maiden, let the crowd fly
Jean Nooner, Cinderella
Make it to the heart
Don't get over it Make your dreams come true
Looner Make your dreams come true Good night Are you having fun? Watch the rest of the show!
This is Halo! I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Beyonce is celebrating the 5th anniversary of her major label debut!
Looking back on this period, tell me about a petty incident that makes you laugh now.
There was a member I couldn't talk to properly for about 6 months.
Ew.
Theater Girls Club View Spy for the performance of the missing attache case
What are you working on right now? What are you especially working on right now for the performance of "Spy A's Gone Attache Case"?
I'm already watching a lot of spy movies, and the trend that I'm noticing for the fall breeze is Dark Academia.
What was the best thing you ate recently? Employee MuscatWhich song stuck out to you personally at the Hello Project 25th anniversary concert the other day?
Juice-Juice's performance of Koboshi Factory's Reminder
Oh!
There are so many things I'm curious about.
It's hard to know which one to mention.
But I'm sure fans are wondering about this too.
That there is a member who couldn't speak for about half a year...
Yes, I was a bit shy and I wasn't really aware of it, but the three members of Seasonings joined the group and I was able to talk to them.
But then the three members of Seasonings joined us, and then there was Reina Uchioka and Shiori Nishida, who were my seniors when I was a trainee at Halo Pro, and then there were the members of Seasonings who joined us.
I don't think I was able to talk to those members properly now.
So I often laugh and talk with my sisters about how I should have talked to them earlier. It's true that I get nervous. At the beginning.
I don't know how to use honorifics well, and I think the older women thought that I was younger than them and that I came in later than them.
I think we were a little awkward with each other for a long time, but not at all.
But now we can laugh about it with a sigh.
What trends are you interested in for the fall and winter season? Yes, it's called Dark Academia.
It's kind of a new subculture that's not really popular in Japan.
It's a little bit like an old mansion or a castle, or a dark atmosphere that's perfect for fall.
I've been looking up fashion items and accessories that have a classic and cute atmosphere that is perfect for fall, and I think that Minami Kawamura would look absolutely adorable in an autumn outfit that incorporates dark academia.
I'm looking forward to seeing it too. I'm so happy.
I have a question for Ms. Ono after the VTR.
Hallo! Ste! Tsubaki Factory, if you're just delusional, you're a free spirit!
me
Tsubaki Factory is fine, Now on sale
Hallo! Ste!
I'd like to ask Ono-san some questions next.
I'd like to ask you a question about the song "It's my life!
It's my life!
At the 25th anniversary concert
I was able to take a picture with Yuko Nakazawa, Yuriko and Rikiu Nakazawa, and also with Yuuki Sato.
What are you working on for Spaki Factory's first overseas tour?
I am watching a lot of vlogs from Hong Kong and Taiwan.
What do you want to try during the fall tour starting in October?
I want to arrange my hair a lot.
What kind of costume do you want to wear for Halloween?
I want to dress up as Professor Snape from Harry Potter.
What was your most memorable moment from the Hello!
I loved Yuko Nakazawa's tears of frustration.
I was able to tell her that I loved it.
Amazing!
Thank you so much!
What are you working on for the overseas tour?
Watching vlogs is one of the things I'm working on.
I've never been abroad.
Is that so?
That's right, I've never been out of Japan.
What should I do to get out of Japan?
I'm going to study vlogging, gourmet vlogging, etc.
I'm going to study those things, too.
I think it's fun to learn a little bit of the language.
I think it's fun to study things like that.
It's wonderful.
Project 25th anniversary concert.
Yuko Nakazawa's tears of regret were a favorite of all Tsubaki Factory members,
At the 20th anniversary concert, there was a time when Yuko Nakazawa sang "Polori (tears of regret)" in Fukuoka,
It was a song that we all fell in love with and loved so much that we played it backstage,
I was happy to be able to tell them that I was happy to hear it again this time.
It was a wonderful exchange.
Thank you very much.
Hallo! We will continue after this.
This is Natsuyaki Masashi.
Here we go.
Hello Kitchen.
This time, I asked this member to come.
Hello!
I am Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 13, I am Ayumi Ishida.
We're going to have fun cooking. Thank you for having us.
Sensei, nice to meet you today. Now, Sensei, what would you like to cook this time?
Today we will make pasta pescatore.
First of all, here are the ingredients for pescatore.
Does that mean you like pasta too?
No, you don't make pasta at all.
On the contrary.
I've never even tried pescatore.
What?
On the contrary.
Because pescatore uses a lot of seafood broth.
Like clams and shizumi (dried sardines).
I'm not that good with clams and shizumi.
But I thought that if I cooked them myself, I could overcome that.
So that's why.
I'd like to take this opportunity.
That's good. I've been thinking about it.
Then let's do our best to make it tasty.
What should we do first?
I think it's faster to boil the water first.
If you boil the water after making the ingredients, you'll have to wait a while.
So let's start with the preparation.
I'll leave it to you.
Yes, let's do it.
The amount of salt is very important.
I have an image of that.
It looks difficult.
Pasta is thin, isn't it?
Today, I have 1.6mm spaghetti.
And now I have 2.4 liters of hot water, so I'm going to add 1% salt to make brine.
I see. That's pretty good.
I'm going to add seaweed.
Should I put salt in the water?
You absolutely have to put it in.
I see.
You definitely have to put it in.
I sometimes hear that you don't have to put it in.
I wonder which one it is.
It has a taste, but...
Taste.
The taste, the taste, the taste.
And the noodles are not tight.
They're a little squishy.
I've never washed shellfish before.
Careful with your hands.
I didn't know they were seashells.
Do you bite them?
No, I don't think it's important.
Even if it was, you wouldn't bite it.
I sometimes bite clams, but I like them a lot. No, I put them away.
You wouldn't chew them even if they were out.
Sometimes you scratch them.
Like clams.
If they're big enough.
It hurts a little bit.
That's true, that's true.
Just a little bit. Just soak it in.
And if you stay in the dark...
It's like you're back in the sand.
The sense of openness should make you open your mouth.
huh?
Here you go.
That's about right?
Yeah.
Is that good?
Yes, sir.
I'll leave it here.
Shrimp curry.
Yes, sir.
And now...
Shrimp.
Yes, sir.
Pescatore is the name of the game.
It's got to have it.
It's important.
It's the star of the show.
It's the star of the show, isn't it?
Yes.
You don't seem to mind at all.
You don't like this one? This is totally fine.
It's fine.
The shell has flavor.
That's right.
So today, I want to leave the shell on.
I want to keep the shell on.
Good!
Very good!
It's okay.
Oh, wow.
I knew you cook on a regular basis.
Now, to the shrimp.
Yes!
I need this.
Let's remove the dorsal fins.
After removing the dorsal fins
Now, let's look at the octopus.
I brought boiled octopus today.
This one is already cooked.
You can eat it as sashimi.
If you cut it into pieces, it's hard to mix with pasta.
It's better to shave it into thin slices.
It's difficult. I'm not very good at it.
I'm totally fine.
Now, I'm using this side of the knife.
Like this.
That's right.
That's all you need to cut.
And if you do it twice...
If you do it twice, the jagged edges will be a little bit wobbly.
But the more jagged it is, the easier it is for the pasta sauce to get into the pasta.
That's right.
I knew that.
I used two cloves of garlic.
Have them split in half. Half split.
There's a core inside, so we remove it.
I don't have to teach you. You're doing it.
You're making tescator for the first time with your mother.
Yes, I'm making tescator for the first time.
Then you do other pastas.
I like garlic.
Yes, garlic. We definitely use garlic in curry.
That's why.
Yes, garlic and ginger...
I use it as a base.
Without it, you can't start without curry.
That's right.
How about this?
We crush it right before.
Just before?
And then, you know, you snap off half of the peppers.
Snap them out.
You know what I'm talking about.
We use one chili pepper.
It's also used for curry.
Yes, okay.
How to make curry.
Like this.
But you can use a jar.
But we don't have a jar.
You know...
When you make curry
With a knife or something.
It's not safe to use a knife.
I understand.
It's a big garlic clove, so it's challenging.
It's low in calories.
I think it's good.
Olive oil.
60cc60cc
Throw in the garlic.
The garlic comes underneath and collects the oil.
I'm already doing that before I tell you.
When it crackles, you turn down the heat.
Wonderful.
It's already starting to color.
Chopsticks, chopsticks, chopsticks.
But, you know, it's a little bit thicker in there.
It's hard to get the heat inside.
So you have to tong-tong-tong it with chopsticks.
and let the oil get inside.
I'll try the sauce.
That's good.
Wow, it looks so good, I don't know what to do.
It sure looks good!
I could eat this by itself.
I can eat it.
So you're not going to make all the pasta at once?
Yes, sir.
You change it once.
Put some chili peppers in here.
Mmm.
Wow...
Interesting.
It's preheated, so it goes in.
Heh.
And there's still some good olive oil left here.
I'll use that too.
We're going to grill the prawns, so we're going to use some of the olive oil that we have left over from the preheating process.
We're going to grill the prawns right here.
We'll start with the spicy one.
I see... I mustn't cook them too quickly.
A little bit of salt, a little bit of salt, a little bit of salt.
Just a little salt.
I didn't think we seasoned the shrimp.
It's fine right here.
Yes, right here is good.
Here's a point for you, Miyamizu.
Don't overcook them.
Yes, this is...
This is, you know, the shrimp...
I want to cook the shells well, but I don't want to cook the meat so much.
but I don't want to overcook the meat.
I see. Why is that?
The meat is too soft and mushy.
The flavor is lost.
It loses its juiciness.
Especially since it's split in half.
When the meat is clear, it's not cooked yet, but when it turns white, it's already cooked.
The meat is.
And at the end, when it is mixed with pasta, it is cooked again, so it should be light.
This is how it's done.
The same goes for all seafood.
Grill the shells thoroughly. It's OK.
Flavor safe, cucumber.
Wow, what a nice aroma.
And, you see, there is still some of the shrimp flavor left in the shrimp,
So, I'm going to leave it as it is without washing.
How about the shijimi? What do you think?
One more time.
That's good.
Then put the shijimi into the place where the flavor of the shrimp is still there.
And then throw in 30 cc of water.
This is, you know, until the mouth opens.
I see. That's the guideline.
Once it opens, it's already cooked.
So it's a little bit like steaming?
I think it's pretty fast.
Maybe a minute or so.
Oh, that fast?
That's right.
Just goo at it.
Oh!
Is everything open?
Almost.
Okay, we're good to go.
Okay, let's open it up now.
Oh, wow.
It's all open.
Wow.
It's almost like the flavor base is set.
Nevermind.
So that's all for this time.
I'll do my best to finish it again next time.
Yes, so please look forward to the next installment!
Oh, good! Bon appétit!
Yum! Delicious!
Yes, I'm already looking forward to the finished product. I'd like to talk about our cooking situation.
Minami, you've been cooking a lot lately, and I guess I'm the one who usually does a lot of cooking, but lately I've been cooking more like, what do you call it, a small bowl of food, rather than a main dish. I'm into the "hee-hee, Oshi-chan! I'm a little bit addicted to "kobachi", which is a kind of accent dish.
Yes, I love boiled eggplant!
Okra with dried bonito flakes on top, or soaked spinach.
I've made a conscious effort to incorporate vegetables into my cooking, and I'm starting to eat more small bowls of food.
Wow, that's very healthy cooking!
I love Japanese food. I don't often cook by myself these days, but recently I made that takikomi-gohan with Shigeru Akiyama.
I don't cook alone much these days, but recently I made that takikomi gohan with Shigeru Akiyama.
It's really filling, like eating the vegetables and chicken, and it's really delicious.
It was really delicious, and I often cook pasta with Shigeru Akiyama.
I often cook pasta with Mo-chan Akiyama, and I hope to be able to cook on my own.
She says she's used to it.
You just love her, don't you?
Action action action!
If you try again and again...
Your body's telling you.
It's not the rhythm.
You'll know if you sing your heart out
It's on fire, it's on fire, it's on fire
It's full of excitement
Be cool with your character
Fanfare of the heart
Harmony of effort and hard work
Lovely and overlapping
Shining and exciting
It's a miracle spell Wow Wow Wow
Even this hard thing that I'm going through
I've got the courage to get over it
I've got the courage to get over it, I'll be fine
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
Getcha Go Go
You've been dreaming about it all year, haven't you?
Step, step, step on the staircase in front of you
I'll repeat it over and over again, and my heart will get stronger
I won't be ego-driven, I won't give up, I'll know when I dance
Halloway, sunshine and white winds
Forget about the sun and the white wind, Sweat it out, smile and be the champion
Harmony of effort and hard work, soon we'll be colorful one tough
Kaki no koe, over the rainbow
Miracle smile Wow Wow
Mountain full of polished speed
Gifu Dojo's mentality
Superb energy
Wow Wow Wow to the center unmanned
Let's Go Go!
I really want to make it happen, and I don't want any regrets
I don't want to have any regrets. I don't want to regret it
Let's keep on shining
Harmony of effort and effort
Overlapping each other so beautifully
Shining and throbbing
Spell the miracle of wow wow wow
No matter how hard things get
I have the courage to overcome
I've got it, so I'll be fine
I'll be safe in the center Wow Wow, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it!
We did it! Honoo Amamizu from Tsubaki Factory
Beyonce Okamura Minami from Amemuro Kawakami presents Halo! Sta.
As I mentioned at the beginning of this article, on September 27th, the day of this distribution, Tsubaki Factory's new single
Organic It's My Life If you're just delusional, you can be free! was released!
Congratulations!
I'd like to introduce a few of the three songs,
It's My Life" is a graduation song for Riko Yamagishi,
It's My Life is Riko Yamagishi's graduation song, and you can hear a lot of her straight and honest voice in the music video.
When all the Tsubaki Factory members watched the music video together, we realized that Riko was graduating.
I think it would be more enjoyable if you could watch it together with the music video viewing party.
I think this song really gives you the courage to take the first step forward.
And if you are just delusional, the dance of "Freedom" is very distinctive and easy to dance to,
I hope many people will dance to it,
Also, in the music video, each of us wore several different costumes.
I wore a jersey and the rest were Heisei gals.
I was given the opportunity to wear costumes in a variety of settings, and there were so many extremes that I thought the range of the costumes was very interesting,
I hope people will pay attention to that.
And what's good, though, is that of the three songs, this is the one that I think shows Tsubaki Factory's character the most,
It's sad, it's a song that makes you care, it's a song that makes you a little sad to listen to,
It is a sad song that makes you feel a little sad, but I hope that you will also pay attention to the sad voices of the band members.
All three songs have different charms, so I hope you will find your favorite one.
I also had a chance to listen to all three songs,
I found Yuki Itsumai Life refreshing,
If it's just fantasy, then Freedom is,
It was so much fun and exciting to watch,
But the song "I like it" is really impressive because of the mature expressions on everyone's faces,
The song "I like it" was very impressive, with the mature expressions on everyone's faces,
Tsubaki Factory's single showed all the charm of each member,
I thought it was a lot of fun to watch.
It's a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Please listen to it as much as you can.
Hallo! STE!
With Mizuho Ono of Tsubaki Factory,
Beyonce, Minami Okamura of Ame no Mori Kawakami, and Mizuho Ono of Tsubaki Factory will be presenting Halo! Ste.
On September 9th and 10th, the 25th anniversary concert of Hello Low Project was held!
Once again, I think it was a gorgeous concert since it was the 25th anniversary of the project.
How was it, Minami?
Yes, I was especially impressed with the performance.
Beyonce performed a super happy song backed by Berikyu, and I never dreamed that Berryz KOBO would also perform at the ℃- performance.
When I was a trainee at Hello Project, I met Beyonce and some of the members of Hello Project came to Hello Project because they admired Berryz KOBO.
I was so happy that all the members of Biong's were able to perform together with Belize KOBO, and it was such a precious experience to see Belicue's cool performance up close.
It was a very precious experience for me to be able to see such a cool performance by Belizekobo up close and personal.
This time, I would like to show you the video of "Hatsukoi Sunrise" from the "all for one and one for all Act II" concert.
Risa Ogata and Nozomi Asakura, who were members of Tsubaki Factory, joined the concert for the first time in a while, and Yume Kishimoto, who was a member of Tsubaki Factory at the time of its major debut, did not join the concert.
Yume Kishimoto could not participate in the performance, but the 8 members from the time of their major label debut performed this song together.
Of course, some things have changed since the rehearsals, but we performed the first number with the members from our major label debut, and the scenery was just as it was in the old days.
I was so happy after a long time that I even cried a little.
We had not been able to sing together until now, so I am very happy that we were able to sing together at this time.
Please take a look at the video.
SALUTE, it's so smooth, I'm getting bitter...
SALUTE
Oh, my God, it's so smooth, I'm getting bitter...
On the way home, I accidentally touched a finger and it was hot.
I don't want to be only a good girl
I don't want to be a bad girl
Freshly grated 8 cm.
I wore heels today
I want to stretch out
I want to touch your love
with all my heart and all my body
When a girl falls in love
can be beautiful
Pretend you don't care and regret it
But it's fun on the flip side
I'm not in love with you. I'm not in love with you.
I've never felt this way before
Oh my god!
I have a feeling something's about to start
I'm writing down the passcodes, Oh my god, I'm gonna find the rhythm, I'm gonna stir it up, I'm gonna stir it up hot
Come on, water staring at my hair, it's turning colors
Blue Tokyo I want to make it bloom brightly
I love you, but it's not enough
I want to feel it over and over again
I want to feel beyond that
First Love Sunrise
I want you to let me out of your heart and let me out of your mind
Cutting through the old world
I don't want to be rude, so I'm gonna get it out
I'll get through the mura, I'll get through the mura
Words are exchanged all over town
Glittering in slow motion
You don't see me as boring
I'm not seen as a lightweight
Little by little, I'm trying to teach my timid self a lesson
You're the top girl in love
You're the top three in love
All you do is fall in love, all you do is worry
You're the top girl in love
I'm sure it's serious business
I want to pull up today's currency so badly
And yet I shouldn't be afraid
This must be love
Love. Breath, breath, son Lesbelle.
Soon I'll get used to it being you
I'll soon get used to it being you.
I want to dye it to that color
I wonder what the sweet and sour taste will be like
The end of a dream I want to try
First boil Sunrise Sunrise
Sunrise
Sunrise Sunrise
I like it when you pretend not to tell me, when you regret it, when you betray me No, it's not that easy
I really want to show you everything I've got
Sometimes I feel like something's about to start
I always wanna run through it
Sometimes every time I stare at it, it turns color
Ah I want to make the chase bloom
Sometimes I always wanna run through
I want to feel what's ahead
1.2.3.4.
You've got a hard time
You've jumped out of the old world
You've gone out of the old world and said you'll never get wet.
You are Mizuho Ono of Tsubaki Factory and Minami Okamura of Bions Ame no Morikawa Umi. It's time for the ending of Halo!
Tsubaki Factory's new single "Courage, it's my life, if you're just delusional, you can be free" has been released today.
The music video can be seen on Tsubaki Factory's official youtube channel, so please watch and listen to it!
Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2023 Autumn Atariyo will start on October 7th. And Tsubaki Factory will be performing overseas on October 14 and 15.
We will perform at Shiga Idol Collection on November 25th and Chikkidensai 2023 on November 26th.
It's been 4 years since we last performed at Shiga Idol Collection, and it's been a long time since we last performed at Chikkadooth Festival, so we will do our best to appeal Tsubaki Factory's charms to everyone who comes to the event. Beyons will perform at the Heian Jingu Shrine Gekiyou Kyoto Meigetsu Concert with Juice-san on September 30.
We will be performing at 2023 Heian Jingu Tsukiyo Yutaka. We are excited to hear that there are many members from Kyoto, including Shiori Nishida and Juice Juice, so it will be a fun concert.
We will also be performing at the Nagaoka Rice 100 Vote Festival Fireworks, Food, Music, and 2023 on October 8.
This will be the first time for me to go to Niigata for a Beyonce event, so I am really looking forward to this concert in Niigata Prefecture.
I am looking forward to eating a lot of rice.
On October 20, I will be performing at the halftime show for the B League game between the Kawasaki Brave Thunders and the Toyama Graugies.
This will be my first halftime show appearance in a while, and I am very much looking forward to supporting the B-League.
And we will be at Osaka Park 3K Hall Breeze from November 23 to 26.
It has been a long time since our performance, so we will do our best to show you our new charm again.
The Hello! Ste is a channel where the members of Hello! Project will appear more and more!
Please subscribe to our channel as new videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
I'm Minami Okamura from Amemurukawa Umi. Bye bye Anne!